<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CBT Practice</string>
    <string name="motto">The best way to prepare for your CBT exams</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>

    <string name="title_1">Get access to past and likely exam questions</string>
    <string name="title_2">Take exams under realistic conditions</string>
    <string name="title_3">Pass your exams by learning from your mistakes</string>

    <string name="message_1">This app allows you to access past and likely questions from the computer based exams of previous years</string>
    <string name="message_2">It simulates real exam conditions with timed sessions and trick questions so that you know exactly how to take your papers on the D-day</string>
    <string name="message_3">With expertly prepared corrections, you\'ll know exactly where you went wrong and pass your exams with flying colours</string>

    <string name="action_departments">Departments</string>
    <string name="action_courses">Courses</string>
    <string name="action_report">Exam Report</string>
    <string name="action_correction">Exam Correction</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="action_test">Exam</string>
    <string name="action_auth">Sign In/Register</string>
    <string name="action_unlock">Unlock CBT Practice</string>
    <string name="action_info">Information &amp; Enquiries</string>
    <string name="action_welcome">@string/app_name</string>

    <string name="fcm_message">FCM Message</string>

    <string name="info">For questions and enquiries on how to get a PIN and fully access the app, join the WhatsApp group or contact any of the people below. A PIN costs ₦200. For information on PIN wholesale opportunities, contact Biodun.</string>
    <string name="whatsapp_group_link">https://chat.whatsapp.com/I9aDaWoaxydJJxcu9f7sQv</string>
    <string name="playstore_link">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.makerloom.ujcbt</string>
    <string name="trial_link">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.makerloom.ujcbtdemo</string>

    <string name="tos_url">https://makerloom.com/terms-of-service/</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_url">https://makerloom.com/privacy-policy/</string>

    <string name="action_timer">00:00</string>

    <!--
    Set these

    <string name="facebook_application_id" translatable="false"></string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme" translatable="false"></string>
    <string name="app_admob_id"></string>
    -->

    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">0</string>
    <string name="default_notification_message_body">Practice for your Exams!</string>

    <string name="action_pay_with_card_bank_ussd_activity">Pay With ATM Card or USSD</string>
    <string name="action_pay_with_airtime_activity">Pay With Airtime</string>
    <string name="action_pay_online_activity">Purchase PIN Online</string>

    <string name="passage_dialog_subtitle">Done</string>
    <string name="passage_dialog_title">Passage</string>
    <string name="inst_dialog_title">Instruction</string>
    <string name="sample_passage">These two factors, the altitude and the weather, tend separately and together to defeat the climber. The height weakens, slows him down, it forces him to spend days and night in the course of his assault on the summit; the weather, besides adding to the demands of his energy and moral fortitude, conspires to deny him thetime he needs to complete his mission. Whereas in lower mountains and on easy ground the weather may be no more than a handicap, in the high Himalayas it is decisive, regardless of terrain. \nThe deduction to be drawn from these two factors was clear enough. We must either so fortify ourselves that we could continue, without detriment, to live our being above limit of natural acclimatization, or better still, we must solve the problem of speed. It was desirable, in fact that we should meet both these requirements and thus give to these chosen to attempt the summit and to their supporting teams some measure of ignorance against the vagaries of the weather, for safety in mountain climbing is as much a matter of swiftness as of sureness of foot. Either or both could be achieved only by the administration of oxygen in sufficient quantities to make up for the deficiency in the air, and for the duration of the upward journey above limit of successful acclimatization.</string>

</resources>
